

# **NANCY VERMA**

# CONTACT

Phone - +91 9779535397

Email - nancyverma396@gmail.com

**Location -** Gurugram (Haryana)

#### Website:

www.nancyverma.me

#### Portfolio:

https://www.behance.net/nancyverma5

#### Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nancy--verma/

### **SKILLS**

- Adobe photoshop
- Figma
- Adobe Illustrator
- CorelDRAW
- Time Management
- Canva
- Leadership & Teamwork

# **EDUCATION**

#### XII- Arts

SS. Model School, Punjabi University 2009-2010

### **Bachelor of Arts**

Punjabi University 2011-2013

# **INTERESTS**

- Cooking
- Dress Designing
- Painting
- Music

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a designer at heart. With **7+ years** of professional experience in graphic design, I specialize in **product branding**, **social media** & **advertising assets**, **and graphics for websites** & **marketplaces**. A creative collaborator and eager learner, I thrive on new challenges.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

LEAD GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Nestasia/ Gurgaon

9/2023 - PRESENT

- Ideating and designing the graphic assets for paid social, website, email campaigns, marketplaces, and other sales & distribution channels
- New graphic assets have resulted in more than 40% growth in ROI of campaigns
- Working on implementing new ideas for seasonal, occasional, and event campaigns
- Consolidated the guidelines and design process for the brand

- ART DIRECTOR

03/2023 - 09/2023

# Innovist/ Gurgaon

- Planned and executed product launches- Bare anatomy, Curly hair range, hair wax; Chemist at Play Body lotion, facewash, face cream and roll-on ranges; SunScoop sunscreen ranges
- Cross-team and external stakeholder collaboration
- Designed advertising assets for Nudge gummies range
- Designed marketplace, advertising, and website assets for existing products of all 4 brands

### SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

03/2022 - 03/2023

## Innovist/ Gurgaon

- Worked on **4 brands'**(Bare anatomy, Chemist at Play, SunScoop and Nudge) social media creatives
- Created landing pages, website & marketplace banners, newsletters, catalogs,
  Ad video frames, gifs, and branding flyers

#### SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

10/2021-02/2022

## Code Brew Labs/ Chandigarh

- Designed website landing pages and worked on social media & Ad creatives
- Client projects- worked on social media & Ad creatives, case studies, pitch decks and infographics (15+ clients, highlight clients: **Bonn, Apni cabs, Healing Hospital**)

## SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

03/2020-10/2021

# Kabera Global Technologies/ Mohali, Punjab

- Designed products' packaging and created mockups
- Worked on 6 brands' social media creatives
- Designed product and website landing pages, Ad videos & banners and catalogs
- Worked on company app's wire frames & designed the screens
- Led a team of 4 people

# GRAPHIC DESIGNER

01/2019-02/2020

# Wings For My Dreams/ Mohali, Punjab

- Worked on Punjab Government project & social media creatives
- Designed catalogs, brochures, flyers, standies, and flex

### GRAPHIC DESIGNER

04/2017-01/2019

- Wellness Solution/Patiala, Punjab
- Designed product packagingWorked on social media creatives
- Designed catalogs, brochures, flyers, standies, and flex